Talking about that icci prudential, the
results for q4 have come in. AP has recorded a decline of about 3%
.  3502 crore AP has been registered
on VONY basis and if we talk about value of new
business, then it has seen an increase of 2.5%,
against 776 crore, 795 crore
on VONY basis and if we
talk about VNB margins, then it has been registered at
22.7% against 21%. The company has declared final dividend at
0.85 paise per share.
Morgan Stanley's report has come.
On EIC Prudential Life, they have given equal weight call
and have given target at 600 per
share. Their value of new
business has been
seen higher than the estimates given in it.
Due to slowdown in Julip growth, AP growth has
seen a decrease. They are also expecting a slow decrease in VNB margins.
Then if we
look at the report of Nomura,
they have given a neutral call and  They have
given a target of 650 for the stock. According to them,
15% growth can be seen in IPRU in fi2
and vNB growth can be
seen better compared to AP.  If we look at Nuvama's report,
they have upgraded the rating to
Buy, which was previously
given as Hold and targeted at
680 per share. If we look at IC Lombard, the
net profit in Q4 results has
decreased by about 2% to Rs 510 crore
net profit on a year-on-year
basis and a 10% increase in gross premium to Rs
6904 crore. Operating
profit has also decreased by about 26%.
Underwriting
loss has been seen at Rs 210 crore on a year-on-year
basis and if we talk about the combine ratio, it has been seen at
about 103%.  Morgan
Stanley's report has come, they have
downgraded the stock to an equal weight rating
and given a target of 1855. The stock has seen a
slowdown in underwriting and lower
investment income,
and limited upside in current valuations due to weak topline growth and
tepid earnings.
Nuvama's report has given a buy call
and given a target. They have cut the target and have put the
stock at 2400 to 2100.